{
    "subject": "resource/Novar_Controls",
    "predicate": "property/products",
    "object": "resource/Building_automation",
    "human_readable": "Novar Controls produces Building automation.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.922793984413147,
            "question": "Besides Novar Controls, are there other companies that produce Building automation?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8348067402839661,
            "question": "What does Novar Controls produce?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.655109703540802,
            "question": "How does Novar Controls' production impact the construction industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3711670935153961,
            "question": "What industry does Building automation belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31224551796913147,
            "question": "How does Building automation contribute to energy efficiency?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27427706122398376,
            "question": "What are some benefits of using building automation systems?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26634398102760315,
            "question": "Are there any challenges associated with implementing building automation?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23102743923664093,
            "question": "Can you give an example of a building automation system?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19350358843803406,
            "question": "What types of buildings commonly utilize Building automation systems?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17305733263492584,
            "question": "What are some future trends in Building automation technology?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Novar Controls produces Building automation.",
            "html": "dbpedia_352_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What types of buildings commonly utilize Building automation systems?",
            "html": "dbpedia_352_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you give an example of a building automation system?",
            "html": "dbpedia_352_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any challenges associated with implementing building automation?",
            "html": "dbpedia_352_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_352_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_352_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_352_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_352_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_352_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_352_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_352_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_352_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_352_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_352_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here is the evaluation of whether the triple \"Novar Controls produces Building automation\" is supported:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because multiple documents mention that Novar solutions are installed in retail, industrial, commercial and education buildings and campuses, and that the company provides advanced building automation programs, specializing in multisite \u201csmart\u201d systems. Additionally, the document for file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_352/re-ranker-msmarco/15.txt explicitly mentions that the Novar ES3.S is a \"fully featured building automation system and energy management solution available for multisite facilities.\""
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple references to Novar Controls Corporation's involvement in building automation and energy management systems, which supports the statement that Novar Controls produces building automation."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}